{ "question": "reserva", "wrong_answer_1":'room', "right_answer":'reservation', "wrong_answer_2":'reception'}
{ "question": "quarto", "wrong_answer_1":'breakfast', "right_answer":'room', "wrong_answer_2":'shower'}
{ "question": "chave", "wrong_answer_1":'restroom', "right_answer":'key', "wrong_answer_2":'room'}
{ "question": "recepção", "wrong_answer_1":'restroom', "right_answer":'front desk', "wrong_answer_2":'meeting room'}
{ "question": "café da manhã", "wrong_answer_1":'break', "right_answer":'breakfast', "wrong_answer_2":'lunch'}
{ "question": "banheiro", "wrong_answer_1":'bed', "right_answer":'restroom', "wrong_answer_2":'door'}
{ "question": "chuveiro", "wrong_answer_1":'door', "right_answer":'shower', "wrong_answer_2":'key'}
{ "question": "cama", "wrong_answer_1":'key', "right_answer":'bed', "wrong_answer_2":'room'}
{ "question": "identidade", "wrong_answer_1":'map', "right_answer":'id', "wrong_answer_2":'door'}
{ "question": "andar", "wrong_answer_1":'card', "right_answer":'floor', "wrong_answer_2":'room'}


    
      